{
  "quizzes": [
    {
      "name": "Beginner Mathematics",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "How many sides are there in a pentagon?",
          "answerChoices": ["4", "5", "6", "7"],
          "correctAnswer": "5"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is: 16 x 16 = ?",
          "answerChoices": ["192", "252", "256", "264"],
          "correctAnswer": "256"
        },
        {
          "question": "How many sides are there in a octagon?",
          "answerChoices": ["5", "6", "7", "8"],
          "correctAnswer": "8"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is: 361 / 19 = ?",
          "answerChoices": ["19", "17", "20.056", "18.05"],
          "correctAnswer": "19"
        },
        {
          "question": "How many sides are there in a star?",
          "answerChoices": ["10", "11", "12", "14"],
          "correctAnswer": "10"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "name": "Advanced Mathematics",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "What is: 21 x 17 = ?",
          "answerChoices": ["273", "331", "336", "357"],
          "correctAnswer": "357"
        },
        {
          "question": "How many sides are there in a heptagon?",
          "answerChoices": ["3", "5", "7", "9"],
          "correctAnswer": "7"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is: 84 / 4 = ?",
          "answerChoices": ["16", "18", "21", "24"],
          "correctAnswer": "21"
        },
        {
          "question": "How many sides are there in a triange?",
          "answerChoices": ["3", "4", "5", "6"],
          "correctAnswer": "3"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is: 11 x 7 = ?",
          "answerChoices": ["71", "77", "78", "79"],
          "correctAnswer": "77"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
